The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Kid,
don't try to put on airs in front of me.
Thunder Celestial Messengers
all have a large number of subordinate families.
They wouldn't have asked me
to give them a Thunder Cauldron like beggars.
Besides,
I have already met
all the Thunder Celestial Messengers
in the Southern Domain of Allheaven !
But you, a mere Ascendant cultivator,
with a fake Thunder Beast
dares to act presumptuously before my Illusory Yin cultivation !?
An Illusory Yin puppet !?
My Zhang family's Mysterious Dark Flame
can even burn
the Origin Souls it touches.
How can this puppet not be affected in the slightest !?
I just want a Thunder Cauldron.
Since he has an Illusory Yin puppet,
he's probably not an ordinary Junior.
If he was a second step cultivator,
then giving him the cauldron would be acceptable.
But I have just broken through to Illusory Yin...
How could I allow myself to get robbed,
and to humiliate our family's name
in front of my Juniors !?
You're shameless !
Does a mere Ascendant cultivator
truly think he can defeat this old man !?
Go !
It seems
I must use my origin energy spells now !
Kid,
you forced my hand !
This Illusory Yin old monster isn't easy to deal with !
Master,
we should run !
The indestructible soul of the Celestial Mountain
is actually starting to melt ?
This spell is unusual.
Weird artifacts
and such incredible Thunder spells !
Who the hell is this kid !?
Wait !
I'll give you a Thunder Cauldron.
Are you willing to exchange
the spell you used just now ?
I've already given you a Thunder Cauldron,
don't push your luck !
If I hadn't just reached Illusory Yin,
you wouldn't have been my match !
If we really fought to the death,
you wouldn't fare well either !
You sent that puppet
to my Planet Sheng Tan ? What are you after ?
Fellow cultivator, rest assured.
I sincerely wish to exchange spells with you.
I learned this spell from a Nirvana Shatterer Senior.
If you find it unworthy,
then let's forget about it.
This spell
is called the Celestial Slaughter Art.
These seals are condensed from the life energy obtained through slaughter
and are almost indestructible.
The Senior who taught me this spell told me
that if someone can have billions of Life Seals protecting their body,
then even if the planet collapses,
they would emerge unscathed.
The defensive power of these seals is astonishing.
It really seems this spell was passed on by a Nirvana Shatterer Senior.
If I could cultivate millions of them for protection,
it would be an excellent life-saving spell.
But the Third-Eye spell
is a family heirloom...
Even if its origin is unclear,
it's a matter of the family's dignity
so it can't be given lightly.
But these Life Seals
really are something else.
Forget it,
since fellow cultivator is unwilling,
I'll drop this matter.
Fellow cultivator, wait !
Deal !
I will exchange with you !
But you must promise
that this Third-Eye spell
must not be passed on to others.
My Third-Eye spell is extremely profound.
I'll just leave a few mistakes in it.
Even if he cultivates it,
he will never reach my level.
After all, he's just a shallow-minded kid.
Within this Third-Eye spell,
there was a trace of the third step.
But he only uses it for slaughter...
He really wasted this treasure.
I traded a flawed Celestial Slaughter Art for this spell...
This transaction
looks almost too good to be true.
Given that old man's wits,
he most likely left errors in it.
But he didn’t realize that
these flaws
are impossible to hide from me.
Everything is ready.
It is time to set out.
The appearance of this Thunder Cauldron
is very similar to the Rain Cauldron from back then.
The method to enter the Thunder Celestial Realm
should also be similar.
It seems like thunder will strike the Thunder Cauldron
in order to transport cultivators into the Thunder Celestial Realm.
Oh my...
This is too much of a commotion
just to transport someone !
Within this thunder, could there be a trace of celestial origin energy ?
This is Celestial Thunder !
Only using this thunder for transporting
would be such a waste.
The origin energy contained within a single strand of Celestial Thunder
would take many years for an ordinary Ascendant cultivator to obtain.
This method of transportation into the Thunder Celestial Realm
is a tremendous opportunity for me.
An opportunity of this magnitude is unheard of.
Today, I will bend the rules of the Thunder Celestial Realm
and devour to my heart's content !
Immortals !?
The Immortal Ancestor has manifested !
The Immortals will bless us !
Immortal, bless us !
Immortal, grant us fortune !
The Ancestor is protecting us.
May Planet Qing Ling's weather calm down,
may the Zhang Family be safe.
Master,
didn't you go too far this time ?
It seems like I did...
This thunder is too powerful,
the Ancient Thunder Dragon can't devour it all.
The Thunder Cauldron was meant for transportation into the Thunder Celestial Realm,
Logically,
the person holding it shouldn't be harmed by the Celestial Thunder.
For now,
I just need to rely on the Thunder Cauldron to channel the thunder
and I can survive this crisis.
That's right !
As expected of Master !
As long as we have the Thunder Cauldron in hand,
no matter how strong the Celestial Thunder is,
it can't harm us at all !
Something's wrong...
According to what Shengong Hu said,
the number of Thunder Cauldrons has always been the same.
They condense from the void and return to the void,
and are never damaged.
Moreover, Thunder Cauldrons are manifestation of the Thunder Celestial Realm itself.
They can't be destroyed by Celestial Thunder !
Master,
if you break this Thunder Cauldron,
wouldn't it mean that from now on,
there would forever be
one less cauldron ?
Thunder Celestial Realm Gate
Tang Yanfeng
Tang Family member
Corporeal Yang
I heard that the famously arrogant Shengong Hu now has a master !
I didn't believe it at first
but since you're here today,
that means you didn't even qualify to use the Thunder Celestial Temple's
teleportation formation.
You must wait with us for the Celestial Gate to open.
It seems this matter really is true.
How could a sparrow know
the lofty ambitions of a swan ?
Back then,
you were the first of the younger generation to become a Messenger.
But now, because your Dao Soul is incomplete,
you've been ostracized by the temple
and criticized by your family's Elders.
I wonder if Brother Shengong's ambitions
really are worth it.
Shengong Hu,
you've really disappointed me !
Even the Grand Elder of the family
has spent his entire life stuck at Nirvana Cleanser
with no hope of progress.
With your narrow-mindedness,
what right do you have to tell me how to live my life ?
Someone ?
He just went right in !?
The Celestial Gate hasn't opened yet,
how could he enter directly ?
Forced entry
will get you struck by Celestial Thunder !
Who the hell was that person ?
He was actually able to force his way before the Celestial Gate opened !
What kind of level
is Master's cultivation at ?
My decision to follow him
was absolutely right !
Fragment of the
Thunder Celestial Realm
Fortunately, the transport Celestial Thunder didn't harm me.
Otherwise, with the might it contained,
my body would've exploded.
From now on, no matter how great the opportunity,
I must not take such risks...
For now, I need some time to heal.
I might as well first use my Divine Sense
to scan this Thunder Celestial Realm
and see how different it is from the Rain Celestial Realm.
Black Mountain Peak
Thunder Celestial Realm
Master Flamespark
Nirvana Shatterer
How interesting...
This is the first time that I have seen
someone barge into the Thunder Celestial Realm like that.
Perhaps...
he is fated with me.
Forget it, forget it,
the main event is more important.
Fated or not,
we'll find out later.
Once the Great Allheaven Formation is complete,
I will sweep through the Cultivation Alliance
and make that old bastard Master Zhong Xuan
die without a grave !
The Thunder Celestial Realm is extremely vast,
far bigger than the Rain Celestial Realm.
According to Shengong Hu,
aside from celestial spells and artifacts,
the two most precious things here are
celestial corpses and origin energy.
Master,
in the Thunder Celestial Realm,
there have been
8 celestial corpses discovered so far.
If someone finds a celestial corpse and hands it to the Thunder Celestial Temple,
they will receive generous rewards from the temple.
As for origin energy,
in the Thunder Celestial Realm,
there are pits rich in natural origin energy.
If a first step cultivator cultivates inside them,
they can greatly shorten the time needed to reach the second step.
In addition,
there is an extremely precious type of items
in the Thunder Celestial Realm called origin tools
that can transform according to the cultivator's cultivation level.
If a first step cultivator obtains it,
it becomes ordinary celestial spiritual energy.
If a second step cultivator finds it,
it transforms directly into origin energy.
Leftover treasures are the rarest things in the world.
It seems like,
I'll need to search carefully.
After several days of healing,
I have repeatedly scanned this place with my Divine Sense.
Why didn't I sense the celestial spiritual energy fluctuations of this object before ?
Could it be...
that the reason origin tools are so hard to find
is because this celestial energy is so peculiar
that it's difficult to detect ?
Junior up ahead,
put down that thing.
If you disobey,
you'll die.
Xu Fenghan
Xu Family member
Illusory Yin
It's not shown what happens after the Thunder Cauldron breaks:
The moment thunder furnace shattered, all of the thunder inside it exploded forth. An unimaginably powerful thunder gushed out and surrounded Wang Lin. This thunder pulled him toward the sky at an extremely fast speed.
This speed was too fast, as if it was trying to tear his body apart!
In almost an instant, this crazy thunder broke through the void and disappeared along with Wang Lin.
Every cultivator with a furnace was being pulled by their respective thunder furnace. Unless they were from the same cultivation planet, the distance between them was far too great to see each other.
When they looked around, aside from the light coming from themselves, it was all just darkness.
However, just at this moment, a powerful ray of thunder flew by like a meteor and carried with it a thunderous roar.
In the novel, Master Flamespark doesn't dismiss Wang Lin like how he did in the donghua. He traps Wang Lin inside a maze spell made of earth tunnels in order to test whether they are fated together or not. If Wang Lin can get out in less than 7 days, then they are fated.
Wang Lin isn't aware that he is being tested so in order to get out of the spell, he had the genius idea of collapsing the entire fragment using all his various artifacts and spells.
“That little guy took the shortcut, or else it would’ve been impossible for him to leave within seven days. However, there is no harm in taking a shortcut. Since you want to become a fated person with this old man that badly, then this old man will reluctantly agree!”
Ask
Qi Condensation
the perilous path filled with countless blades.
Foundation Establishment
Can the mundane world be shattered
Core Formation
Nascent Soul
by a child's steadfast heart ?
If the laws of this world
Soul Formation
Soul Transformation
stand in the way,
I'll defy the universe to tread the heavens
Ascendant
and ask this question to the sky.
My heart's deepest wish
is to not kneel before these mountains and rivers.
Don't accept your doomed fate,
karma can be changed.
Unwilling to let go,
my obsessions propel me forward.
Don't be afraid.
Thunder rumbles as I dare to tread through the reincarnation cycle.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.
Accept your fate and stay mortal or defy it to become immortal.
Hold fast to this resolve and break through the obstacles.
I'll fight all those who dare to stand in my way.
Let the winds of war heed my command.
I sign this question with my heart.
What is the Dao ?
Defying the flow of heaven and earth,
the heart I cultivate stays true.
I contemplate the wisdom of heaven and earth.
I shall choose my path between karma and fate.
My unshakable Dao Heart
aspires to ascend.
Defying,
this is what my journey to treading the heavens relies on.